<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Laravel - Category - Un ingeniero de software, backend developer, PHP y Python.</title>
        <link>https://www.fernando.info/categories/laravel/</link>
        <description>Laravel - Category - Un ingeniero de software, backend developer, PHP y Python.</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 20:08:40 &#43;0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.fernando.info/categories/laravel/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>I dont use it, I give it away for free</title>
    <link>https://www.fernando.info/free-ads/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 20:08:40 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.fernando.info/free-ads/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Full PHP ads script created using Laravel framework where users donate things that don&rsquo;t use anymore and want to I give it away for free.</p>
<p>Features:</p>
<ul>
<li>Register / login system.</li>
<li>Add, edit, remove ads.</li>
<li>Search engine by keyword and/or state.</li>
<li>Ad private message system between donor and interested person.</li>
<li>Rating system between donor and reciever when deal is finished and object is delivered.</li>
<li>Note: script is actually translated only in Spanish, sorry.</li>
</ul>
<p>Proyecto desarrollado en PHP utilizando el framework de Laravel de anuncios de objetos que ya no se utilizan y se ofrecen como regalo a otros usuarios que lo puedan necesitar. &ldquo;Quiero regalar algo&hellip; que ya no necesito y que puede ser útil para otra persona.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Características:</p>
<ul>
<li>Sistema de registro e identificación de usuarios.</li>
<li>Crear, mofificar, eliminar anuncios publicados.</li>
<li>Buscador por palabras y/o ciudad.</li>
<li>Mensajería privada por cada anuncio entre el autor y cada persona interesada.</li>
<li>Sistema de valoraciones entre usuarios por cada trato cerrado tras la entrega del objeto regalado.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://loregalo.herokuapp.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer">Online demo</a></p>
<p><a href="https://github.com/fernandod1/Fre-ads" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer">Download script and screenshots</a></p>]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
