<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Posts - Un ingeniero de software, backend developer, PHP y Python.</title>
        <link>https://www.fernando.info/posts/</link>
        <description>Posts | Un ingeniero de software, backend developer, PHP y Python.</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 20:08:40 &#43;0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.fernando.info/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Meeting room booking system</title>
    <link>https://www.fernando.info/meeting-room-booking-system/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 08:27:40 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.fernando.info/meeting-room-booking-system/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>PHP script to manage a meeting room booking system. Some of it&rsquo;s features:</p>
<ul>
<li>Added calendar to select any date.</li>
<li>Script configured to assign best room acording to number of persons and capability.</li>
<li>Not MySQL database required. Data stored in plain text files.</li>
</ul>
<p>Script en PHP simula un sistema de reserva en franjas horarias de salas de reuniones. El escript optimiza la asignación de sala en función de la capacidad de la sala y del número de personas que deben reunirse, asignado la sala con capacicidad mínima que cumpla el número de personas requeridas.</p>
<p><a href="https://github.com/fernandod1/Meeting-room-booking-system" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer">Download script</a></p>]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Domains .ES expiration monitoring and backorder</title>
    <link>https://www.fernando.info/domains-es/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 04:57:40 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.fernando.info/domains-es/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Live monitoring .ES domains expiration and execute domain backorder as soon as expired. Notify spanish domains (.ES) expiration. For example, you can use registrants API to register domain instantly (domain backorder) &amp; catch it!</p>
<p>Script en python que realiza un monitoreo continuado de la expiración del registro de un dominio .ES con el fin de realizar un backorder en el momento preciso para obtener el dominio de interés.</p>
<p><a href="https://github.com/fernandod1/DomainES-backorder" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer">Download script</a></p>]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Expiring link generator with control panel &amp; stats</title>
    <link>https://www.fernando.info/expiring-links-generator/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 03:57:40 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.fernando.info/expiring-links-generator/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Full PHP script with admin control panel to generate expiring links to keep track and stats of ad campaigns or other links stuff. When link expires (reach maximum number of clicks configured), script may redirects traffic to an alternative link like <a href="http://www.disney.com">www.disney.com</a> or print &ldquo;Expired campaign&rdquo; message.</p>
<p>FEATURES:</p>
<ul>
<li>Admin login page</li>
<li>Admin control panel</li>
<li>Create / delete new expiration links</li>
<li>Daily stats of eack link clicks</li>
<li>Custom link to track clicks</li>
<li>Custom javascript code you can insert into any webpage to print in real time nº of clicks a link recieves.</li>
</ul>
<p>Script completo en PHP con panel de administración que permite generar enlaces personalizados que caducan al alcanzarse X clicks. Puede insertarse en un sitio web y obtener estadísticas diarías sobre el número de clicks recibidos en una campaña. El script genera un códido javascript personalizado que podrá insertarse en una página web externa y mostrará un contador con el total de clicks recibidos en campaña.</p>
<p>Cuando la campaña expira, el enlace personalizado al ser visitado podrá mostrar un mensaje de &ldquo;Campaña finalizada&rdquo; o redirigir el tráfico a otra dirección web.</p>
<p><a href="https://github.com/fernandod1/Expiring-link-generator" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer">Download script and screenshots</a></p>]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Instagram to Discord post images</title>
    <link>https://www.fernando.info/instagram-to-discord/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 02:57:40 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.fernando.info/instagram-to-discord/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>This python script executes 2 actions:</p>
<ul>
<li>Monitors for new image posted in an instagram account (must create a cronjob).</li>
<li>If found new image, a bot posts new instagram image into a discord channel.</li>
</ul>
<p>Script en python que monitoriza un cuenta de instagram y cuando es publicada una imagen, realiza su pulicación simultánea en un canal de Discord mediante webhook.</p>
<p><a href="https://github.com/fernandod1/Instagram-to-discord" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer">Download script</a></p>]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Instagram images/videos downloader</title>
    <link>https://www.fernando.info/instagram-downloader/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 01:57:40 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.fernando.info/instagram-downloader/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Instagram user&rsquo;s photos and videos downloader python script. Download all media files from any public username.</p>
<p>Script en python para descargar todas las imágenes y videos de un usuario de Instagram.</p>
<p><a href="https://github.com/fernandod1/Instagram-downloader" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer">Download script</a></p>]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Countries IP block web access</title>
    <link>https://www.fernando.info/country-ip-block-web-access/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 01:05:40 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.fernando.info/country-ip-block-web-access/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>PHP script with control panel to block web access from certain countries of your choosing. It uses <a href="http://api.hostip.info">http://api.hostip.info</a> IP Location API.</p>
<p>Script con panel de control que permite configurar y bloquear el acceso desde determinados países a determinadas páginas web PHP. Hace uso de la API de IPs de paises de <a href="http://api.hostip.info">http://api.hostip.info</a>.</p>
<p><a href="https://github.com/fernandod1/Country-IP-block-web-access" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer">Download script and screenshots</a></p>]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>I dont use it, I give it away for free</title>
    <link>https://www.fernando.info/free-ads/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 20:08:40 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.fernando.info/free-ads/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Full PHP ads script created using Laravel framework where users donate things that don&rsquo;t use anymore and want to I give it away for free.</p>
<p>Features:</p>
<ul>
<li>Register / login system.</li>
<li>Add, edit, remove ads.</li>
<li>Search engine by keyword and/or state.</li>
<li>Ad private message system between donor and interested person.</li>
<li>Rating system between donor and reciever when deal is finished and object is delivered.</li>
<li>Note: script is actually translated only in Spanish, sorry.</li>
</ul>
<p>Proyecto desarrollado en PHP utilizando el framework de Laravel de anuncios de objetos que ya no se utilizan y se ofrecen como regalo a otros usuarios que lo puedan necesitar. &ldquo;Quiero regalar algo&hellip; que ya no necesito y que puede ser útil para otra persona.&rdquo;</p>
<p>Características:</p>
<ul>
<li>Sistema de registro e identificación de usuarios.</li>
<li>Crear, mofificar, eliminar anuncios publicados.</li>
<li>Buscador por palabras y/o ciudad.</li>
<li>Mensajería privada por cada anuncio entre el autor y cada persona interesada.</li>
<li>Sistema de valoraciones entre usuarios por cada trato cerrado tras la entrega del objeto regalado.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://loregalo.herokuapp.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer">Online demo</a></p>
<p><a href="https://github.com/fernandod1/Fre-ads" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer">Download script and screenshots</a></p>]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Laser hair removal control panel to manage client&#39;s treatments</title>
    <link>https://www.fernando.info/laser-hair-removal-control-panel/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 20:07:40 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.fernando.info/laser-hair-removal-control-panel/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Full PHP script control panel to manage client&rsquo;s database and sessions of laser hair removal treatments in a beauty center.</p>
<p>Features:</p>
<ul>
<li>Add, edit, remove clients.</li>
<li>List all clients or search one client.</li>
<li>Upload system of client&rsquo;s disclaimer treatment documents.</li>
<li>Add, remove new treatment to client. (Mode just one session or Pack of 5 sessions (&ldquo;bonus pack&rdquo;)).</li>
<li>Consume session of client.</li>
<li>Counter of sessions left of each treatment of client.</li>
<li>Option &ldquo;pay before session treatment&rdquo; or &ldquo;pending payment&rdquo; label reminder).</li>
<li>Note: script is actually only translated to spanish, sorry.</li>
</ul>
<p>Script completo en PHP consistente en un panel de administración de clientes de un centro de depilación láser. Permite llevar la administración de los servicios contratados y sesiones consumidas por cada cliente.</p>
<p>Características:</p>
<ul>
<li>Añadir, modificar, y eliminar clientes.</li>
<li>Listado de clientes o búsqueda individual.</li>
<li>Sistema para subir fichero de documentación de descarga de responsibilidad de cada cliente.</li>
<li>Añadir o eliminar tratamientos de depilación láser a clientes. (Ejemplo: sesión simple o bono de 5 sesiones).</li>
<li>Consumo de sesión de cliente.</li>
<li>Contador de sesiones disponibles sin consumir de cada tratamiento de cliente.</li>
<li>Opciones &ldquo;pagado antes de sesión&rdquo; o recordatorio de &ldquo;pago pendiente&rdquo;.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://github.com/fernandod1/Laser-hair-removal-app" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer">Download script and screenshots</a></p>]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Covid-19 daily report in Spain</title>
    <link>https://www.fernando.info/covid-19-spain/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 21:57:40 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.fernando.info/covid-19-spain/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>PHP script displaying daily reports/stats about Covid-19 virus status in Spain and its states. Data is collected from API of Ministerio de Sanidad of government of Spain.</p>
<p>Script en PHP que muestra los datos diarios de infectados de Covid-19 en España realizando extrayendo la información de la API proporcionada por el Ministerio de Sanidad del gobierno de España.</p>
<p><a href="https://covid19espana.herokuapp.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer">Online demo</a></p>
<p><a href="https://github.com/fernandod1/Covid-19-Spain" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreffer">Download script</a></p>]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
